(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down, could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB. Can't you feel your own frustration?
You're a MOB. What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions on your sleeve and break it down.
What do you see once you go beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9!)
The mysterious percentage.
Cryin' my life, cryin' my psyche,
cryin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100.
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind? Right now...
Your life is your own.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
Mob Psycho
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
The Battle for Social Rehabilitation
~Friendship~
Leave. I don't want you to get hurt.
（芹沢(せりざわ)）
帰ってくれ
ケガさせたくないんだよね
You can take this guy back with you, too.
このおじさん
連れて帰っていいから―
He's supposed to be a hostage,
一応 人質なんだけど
ちょっと かわいそうだし
but I feel bad for him.
Oh, it's the prime minister guy.
（モブ）
あっ 総理大臣の人だ
What? You're the prime minister?!
（芹沢）
えっ？　あんた 総理大臣なの？
（矢部(やべ)総理大臣）
い… 行っていいのか？
I-I'm free to go?
Go right ahead.
（芹沢）
どうぞ
スゲえ
総理大臣と会話しちゃったよ
Holy cow... I just talked
to the prime minister!
（モブ）
犯行の当事者なのに
知らなかったのか
You're part of the group that abducted him,
and you had no idea?
Well, you know, I don't watch TV.
（芹沢）
俺 テレビとか見ないし…
I see. So the public thinks
we're the bad guys.
そっか　俺たちは
世間じゃ 悪者扱いなんだなあ
But you are, though. Look at
how much damage you've done to the city.
（モブ）
っていうか悪者ですよ
あんなに町を壊して
It's fine. The president said that
most people had already evacuated.
（芹沢）
大丈夫だよ
“大半の人は避難済みだった”って
社長も言ってたし
（エクボ）
社長？
President?
俺を雇ってくれた人だよ
The person who hired me.
俺を腐ったドブ沼の底から
救い上げてくれたんだ
He rescued me from
the hellhole that was my life.
3 Years Ago
Serizawa Katsuya
27 years old
It's filthy in here. Why have you
been a shut-in for fifteen years?
（鈴木(すずき)）
汚いな　15年もなぜ引きこもる？
Who're you?
（芹沢）
あんた 誰？
私は鈴木という者だ
My name is Suzuki.
君のお母さんから相談を受けてな
Your mother asked me to help you.
Another counselor?
（芹沢）
また相談所の人か
Just know that if you get any closer,
you'll get hurt.
言っとくけど
それ以上 近寄ったらケガするよ
I'm not normal.
俺 普通じゃないんだよ
君は超能力者だそうだな
分かるよ 君の気持ちは
I hear that you're an esper.
I understand how you feel.
（芹沢）
あ～ 無理　帰ってくれ
Yeah, no. Go away.
Why? Why don't you tell me
how you're feeling?
（鈴木）
どうしてだ？
君の思いの丈を
聞かせてくれないか？
（芹沢）
うっ ダメだ　それ以上しゃべるな
No... Don't say anything else.
Please, I'm begging you. Don't annoy me.
頼むから
俺をイライラさせないでくれ
It must be hard...
（鈴木）
つらいよなあ
not being able to make friends
because people find your powers creepy.
超能力を気味悪がられて―
友達も出来ず…
Potato Chips
Yeet Tea
Stop. Don't act like you know how I feel.
（芹沢）
やめろ！
知ったふうなことを言わないでくれ
Go away! Just go away!
帰れ！　帰れよ！
You must've been bullied
out of your place in society.
（鈴木）
いじめられて 社会に居場所が
ないんじゃないかって…
Get out!
出てけよ～！
I'm an esper too, you see.
（鈴木）
私も超能力者なんだ
Come with me.
私と共に来い
で… でも 俺
部屋を出ると めまいがして…
B-But I get dizzy whenever I leave my room.
It was raining outside.
（鈴木）
外は雨が降っていた
これは君の分の傘だ
This umbrella is for you.
この傘の下が
君の部屋だと思えばいい
Just imagine that when you're under
this umbrella, you're in your room.
Don't worry. You'll be fine if you're with me.
安心しろ
私のそばにいれば大丈夫だ
I'll show you how to use your powers.
“力”の使い方を教えてやる
After that, I became an
upper echelon employee of Claw
（芹沢）
以来 俺は
この“爪”の幹部社員として―
and regained my place in society.
社会に復帰できたというわけだ
That's weird.
（モブ）
おかしい話だな
Huh?
Even I can tell that's all kinds of wrong.
（モブ）
僕でも
それがおかしな話だって分かる
それって
利用されてるだけなんじゃないかな
Aren't you basically just being used?
（エクボ）
おお！　茂夫がそれを言うか？
Look who's talking!
What a horrible thing to say...
なんてひどいことを言うんだ 君は
You're the one who's horrible.
（モブ）
ひどいのは そっちだ
If this is what you were going to do,
you should've just stayed a shut-in.
こんなことをするなら
引きこもってるほうが全然いいよ
Can't you picture the faces of
the people impacted by this?
（モブ）
困ってる人の顔が浮かばないのか？
The president said that world domination
always involved certain sacrifices.
（芹沢）
社長は世界征服に犠牲は付き物だと
言ってたな
Do you believe that, too?
（モブ）
自分も そう思うの？
（芹沢）
あ～ 帰ってくれないかなあ
Hey... could you leave?
芹沢さん あんた
ついていく人を間違えたよ
Serizawa-san, you chose
the wrong person to follow.
You okay?
大丈夫か？
That umbrella...
あの傘
Yeah, it's shrouded in some insane power.
ああ とんでもないパワーを
まとってるぜ
I can relax when I'm under this umbrella.
（芹沢）
この傘の中にいれば
俺は安心なんだ
If we can take his umbrella...
あの傘を奪えば…
戦力を失うってか？
He'll lose his strength.
えい！
Trying to immobilize me...
isn't going to work!
金縛りは効かないよ！
（打撃音）
（モブ）うっ 痛い
Ow...
Oh, sorry. Are you okay?
ご… ごめん 大丈夫かい？
Wait, you were faking?
（芹沢）
あっ 嘘か！
Now, Dimple!
（モブ）
今だ エクボ！
You got it!
よし きた！
Oh, shit!
ヤベえ！
一瞬 傘を失っただけで
今のありさまかよ
He explodes after only a second
without his umbrella?
きっと不安でしょうがないんだよ
He must be incredibly anxious.
He finally found someone
who understood him.
（モブ）
やっと現れた理解者なんだ
He had no choice but to follow him.
すがりつくしかない
He never stood a chance against someone
who used that to their advantage.
（モブ）
その心の隙間につけ込まれたら
きっと ひとたまりもない
I have to tell him.
教えてあげなきゃ
That president of yours
didn't give you peace.
あんたの社長は
安心を与えてくれたんじゃなくて
自分１人じゃ生きていけない
っていう不安を与えて―
He gave you the idea that
you can't live on your own
組織に縛りつけてるんだ
and chained you to the organization.
ハハハ 君はカウンセラーか？
Are you a counselor?
You can't reintegrate into society this way.
社会復帰なんてできない
むしろ このままじゃ
余計に取り返しがつかなくなる
If anything, at this rate,
you'll never be able to return.
未来ある若者が
知ったようにしゃべってくれるな
Like a kid who still has his whole future
ahead of him knows how I feel.
だったら―
Then tell me... What the hell
am I supposed to do?!
だったら どうしろって言うんだ！
No one understood this power
I was born with!
生まれつきの特性を
誰にも理解されず―
（芹沢）
気味悪がられて―
People thought I was creepy,
so I'd lose control and cause people trouble!
暴走して 迷惑をかけて
And because of that,
I'd get scorned and lose control again!
蔑(さげす)まれて また暴走して！
I even accidentally sent
my mother flying before!
母ちゃんを
吹っ飛ばしたことだってあるんだ
I never had any idea
when I might lose control!
いつ暴走するのか
自分でも分からない
ろくに人と話すことができなかった
I couldn't even talk to anyone...
I just...
俺は ただ―
I dunno... I just wanted...
何というか その…
I just wanted friends.
友が―
仲間が欲しかった
ここには仲間がいるんだ
I have friends here.
同じような超能力者が！
Espers just like me!
君には分からない！
You'd never understand!
Of course I understand.
They aren't your friends.
（モブ）
分かるさ　そんなの仲間じゃない
僕には仲間がいるからね
I actually have friends.
That's how I know.
（モブ）
だから 分かる
They aren't your friends.
そんなの仲間じゃない
Stop... Stop saying that over and over!
な… 何回も言うな～！
ヤベえぞ 茂夫(しげお)！
スゲえエネルギーだ
This isn't good, Shigeo!
That's an insane amount of energy!
I won't let you go any further!
Those are the president's orders!
この先へは行かせない！
社長の命令だ
The president trusts me!
社長は俺を信頼しているんだ
いや そんなの信頼関係じゃない
No, it has nothing to do with trust.
You're just being used.
あんたは都合よく利用されてるんだ
違う！
No! The president gave me a reason to live!
社長は俺の存在価値を
見いだしてくれたんだ
But he doesn't see you as a person!
でも あんたの人間味は見てない！
人間味？
As a person?
（モブ）
ケガさせたくないって
言ってたじゃないか
You said you didn't want to hurt anyone.
You're just like me.
僕と同じだ
I know you realize
本当は気付いてるはずだ
that you're wrong.
自分が間違ってること
Shut up!
うるさ～い！
In that case... I'll be your friend.
だったら
僕があなたの友達になる！
Huh?
Whoops...
I shot at him.
（芹沢）
撃っちゃった
Shigeo!
茂夫～！
つい 本気で…
I even went all out!
What?!
なに！
俺のエネルギーを
吸収しているのか？
You're sucking up my energy?
I can sense what you're feeling.
感情が伝わってくる
なんて悲しいエネルギーだ
Such a sad energy...
自分の“力”に変換したのか？
You turned it into your own power?
No. You can have it back, Serizawa-san.
いいや 返すよ 芹沢さん
What is this?
（芹沢）
何だ これは？
I see...
そうか　彼も俺と同じ
He's...
He's the same as me...
Friendship
Now I'm going to have to recruit more
soldiers because of you and your friends.
（鈴木）
お前たちのせいで―
また戦闘員を
補充しないといけなくなった
（ショウ）
もうやめろよ おやじ
Stop this already, Dad.
You can see that they aren't much help.
（ショウ）
大した戦力にならないのは
今回で分かっただろ
息子のお前にだけ特別に教えてやる
Since you're my son,
I'll go ahead and tell you.
The project of applying stress
to normal human beings
（鈴木）
ノーマルの人間にストレスを加えて
超能力を覚醒させる実験
to awaken any ESP they may have...
It was a failure.
あれは失敗だ
Even if they did happen
to awaken to some powers,
仮に“力”を目覚めさせても―
the most they could do was produce
some insignificant phenomenon.
せいぜい
軽微な現象を起こすのが関の山だ
Then their powers...
（ショウ）
じゃあ ヤツらの“力”は？
You call that an insignificant phenomenon?
あれも軽微な現象ってやつなのか？
彼らが我が物顔で扱っている“力”
The powers they're using
like they're going out of fashion
あれは私の“力”だ
are my powers.
I am able to share my power with others.
（鈴木）
自分のエネルギーを
他人に分け与えることができ
At the same time, I am able to absorb
other people's powers as my own.
また 他人のエネルギーを
自分の中に取り込むこともできる
This is my true trump card
that no one knew about.
これが 誰にも知られていない
真の切り札だ
So you gave 600 soldiers your power?
600人の兵隊に
“力”を与えてたってのか？
（鈴木）
あんなものは―
That's just a mere fraction of
the energy that I have accumulated.
私のためてきたエネルギーの
ほんの一部にすぎない
だが それも
貴重なエネルギーに変わりはない
But that doesn't make it any less vital.
I'll be reclaiming my energy
from those who have lost.
敗北者たちからは返却してもらおう
い… 今 分かった
I-I finally understand...
My dad's not human.
（ショウ）
おやじは人間じゃねえ
He's a monster made up of energy!
エネルギーの怪物だ！
Let this be a lesson, Sho.
肝に銘じておけ ショウ
Only one absolute being can be
the true protagonist of this world.
世界の主役になれるのは―
たった１人の
絶対者だけだということを
Absolute being?
（ショウ）
絶対者
あ… お前は！
You're—
Mob Psycho
律(りつ)の兄貴か
You're Ritsu's older bro.
That must mean my detonator
went off successfully.
ということは―
俺の仕掛けた“起爆剤”は
うまく着火したのか
Are you the one who set fire to my house?
もしかして
家に火を付けたのは君？
ヘッ 怒ってるとこ悪(わり)いけど―
You're probably pissed off about that,
but you should probably run.
もう逃げたほうがいいぜ
There's no one in this world
who can defeat him.
あんなのに勝てる人間は
この世にいねえ
I'm not mad anymore.
I'm sure you have a lot going on.
もう怒ってないよ
君にもいろいろあるんでしょ
実のお父さんに
そんなにやられるなんて…
I mean, look at what
your own father has done to you.
Who are you?
（鈴木）
何者だ？
He's been worried about you
losing control. I can tell.
（モブ）
彼は
あんたの暴走に悩んでいたんだ
僕には分かる
Because my younger brother
was afraid of me, too.
僕の弟も 僕におびえていたから
He's... changed.
（ショウ）
こいつ 変わったな
You make it sound like you know
what's going on with our family.
（鈴木）
他人の家庭内事情を
知ってるような口ぶりだな
芹沢さんに聞いた
Serizawa-san told me that
your son was trying to stop you.
息子が父親を止めようとしてること
That your son was being beaten so badly,
（モブ）
返り討ちに遭っている様子が
見るに堪えなくて
he couldn't bear to watch
and came downstairs...
階段を下りてきたこと
That he felt so pathetic
for not being able to step in,
仲裁できなかった自分が情けなくて
消えたくなったこと
making him want to disappear.
芹沢が負けたというのか
Serizawa lost?
That moron. He must've gotten sloppy.
ヤツめ 手を抜いたな
違うよ
You're wrong.
Winning and losing
勝つとか負けるとか―
isn't the be all and end all
in relationships between people.
人と人との関係は
そればっかりじゃないんだよ
It was the president
who got me out of that room.
（芹沢）
俺を部屋から出してくれたのは
社長だ　感謝はしてる
I'm grateful to him.
But why is there a need to hurt people?
でも どうして
人を傷つける必要があるんだろう
I've been too scared to think about it
so I've been running away...
深く悩むことが怖くて
逃げていたけど―
But if my happiness only came
as a result of another's tears,
裏で誰かが泣いてまで
得られる充実なんて―
最初から求めていなかった
I never wanted it in the first place.
気付かせてくれて ありがとう
Thank you for making me realize that.
やはりクズは 一生クズのままか
Apparently, trash will never be
anything more than trash.
So be it. It's not like I ever truly
counted on others to begin with.
（鈴木）
まあ いい
最初から他人など当てにしていない
Bonds with others are absolutely meaningless.
人とのつながりなど
意味のないものだ
After all, I am whole on my own.
私は１人で
存在が完成しているのだから
That's not true. Everyone...
（モブ）
それは違う
誰だって―
人は多くの人と関わって
成長していくんだ
Everyone grows because of their
encounters with other people.
人には人が必要なんだ
People need other people.
Someday, you'll need others.
いつか誰かが必要になる
きっと そのときには後悔するんだ
When that time comes,
you're surely going to regret things.
So if you don't have anyone to talk to,
だから
もし相談相手がいないのなら―
I'll be there.
（モブ）
僕が…
You want to be a shoulder I can lean on?
私の相談相手に？
フフフ そういうことは
他の弱者とやってくれ
Save that kind of talk
for the weaklings of the world.
Ritsu's bro, he can give people his energy
and steal theirs in turn.
律の兄貴
ヤツはエネルギーを
他人に与えたり奪ったりできる
On top of that, he's got
a massive stock of energy himself.
（ショウ）
それに加えて
大量のエネルギーのストックがある
Meanwhile, I can barely even move...
こっちは もうガス欠で
動けもしねえってのに…
Will this help you move?
これで動けるようになる？
What?
（ショウ）
なに？
Th-This is...
こ… これは！
（鈴木）
おお！　私と同じ“力”を！
He has the same power as me?
Can you move?
（モブ）
動ける？
Y-Yeah, I can sorta stand.
（ショウ）
あ… ああ なんとか立てるぜ
よかった　じゃあ 君も避難してよ
That's good. In that case,
you should evacuate, too.
僕は もう少し…
I'm going to—
I have acknowledged you as my enemy.
（鈴木）
お前を敵と見なす！
Stop!
（ショウ）
やめろ！　あっ！
You stay out of this.
引っ込んでろ
こいつは私の天敵になりうる
He has the potential to
become my mortal enemy.
Don't. I came here to talk.
やめろ！　僕は話し合いに来たんだ
反撃しろ 茂夫！
こういうヤツには何を言っても…
Give it up, Shigeo!
You can't talk to guys like—
You're an annoyance.
（鈴木）
目障りだ　先に消えろ
（エクボ）
貴様ぁ！
You can disappear first.
（鈴木）
目障りだ　先に消えろ
Dimple!
エクボ！
Was it really a good idea to
let Kageyama-kun go off alone?
（テル）
影山(かげやま)君を１人で行かせて―
よかったんだろうか
（影山(かげやま) 律(りつ)）
あんなに自分の意思を
表に出した兄さんは 初めて見た
I've never seen my brother
openly stamp his authority like that.
He looked in pain to me, though.
（テル）
僕にはあれが つらそうに見えたよ
もともとは
先頭に立つタイプじゃないはずだ
He's not usually the type to fight.
どう思いますか？　霊幻(れいげん)さん
What do you think, Reigen-san?
At first glance, Mob looks pretty unreliable,
but his strength is undeniable.
（霊幻(れいげん)新隆(あらたか)）
モブは はたから見れば頼りないが
強い力を持ってる
（誇山(こやま)）
バカげた出力の念動力だろ？
His insane telekinesis, right?
That's just one of his qualities.
（霊幻）
そんなもんは あいつの持ってる
特徴の１つにすぎない
What makes him truly great
あいつが本当にすごいのは―
is his ability to tell people
exactly how he feels.
人に感情を伝えられるところだ
And that speaks to their heart
far more than any niceties.
それは
どんなに取り繕った言葉よりも響く
As long as Mob's feelings can be
expressed to whoever he's facing...
モブが抱く感情が
相手に伝わりさえすれば…
（霊幻）エクボ！
（つかむ音）
Dimple!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
どうした 大丈夫か？　モブは？
Where's Mob?
分からねえが 結構ヤバそうだ
I'm not sure, but things look pretty grim.
The enemy was pretty intent
on mercilessly killing Shigeo.
（エクボ）
敵は ちゅうちょなく
茂夫を殺す気だったぞ
Four-eyes, you got a sec?
(霊幻)
メガネ！　ちょっといいか？
（鈴木）
ふん 話し合いだと？
Talk?
You said that bonds with others
are meaningless.
（モブ）
人とのつながりが意味ないなんて
言ったじゃないか
That can't be true.
そんなわけないだろ
Everyone lacks something.
人は みんな
どこか足りないものがあって―
People making up for others' deficiencies
is what makes this world go around.
それを補い合って世界が出来てる
つまらんな お前たちは
All of you are so boring.
Even among those
blessed with the gift of ESP,
（鈴木）
超能力を持つ者―
その有利な条件を得た者の中でも
私は
さらに強い“力”を持っている
my powers far surpass them all.
When I came to that realization,
その事実に気付いたとき―
it appeared as though this world
could fit in the palm of my hand.
この世界が
手のひらサイズに見えたよ
That was when I was in middle school,
same as the two of you.
（鈴木）
ちょうど お前たちと同じ
中学のころだな
But your mindset
puts a halt to all progress,
だが お前の考え方では
歩みは そこで止まり―
leaving you living a boring life
just like the powerless.
無能力者どもと同じ
つまらん人生を過ごすことになる
That's not true.
違う
中学生のころから止まっているのは
あんたのほうだ
You're the one who's stopped in place
since middle school.
There are far more unique people
in this world than you think,
（モブ）
自分が考えてる以上に
世の中には いろんな人がいて―
and just as many mindsets.
いろんな考え方がある
No one should be able to place a value
on another person's mindset.
人の考え方に点数なんて
誰も付けられないはずなんだ
まるで道徳の授業だな
You sound like you're trying
to take the moral high ground.
I have no need to rely on others
to make up for my deficiencies
（鈴木）
足りないものを補い合う生き方は
私には必要ない
because I have the ability
to steal, use, and rule.
奪い 利用し 支配する力を
持っているからだ
My goal in life is to leave
a huge mark upon this world.
この世界に大きな爪痕を残すことが
私の人生の目標なのだよ
Ritsu's bro,
（ショウ）
律の兄貴
構わねえから やっちまってくれ
don't worry about me. Just finish him off!
Sho, I'd thought about letting you inherit
the world I was going to take over,
（鈴木）
ショウ
お前には 私が支配する世界を
継がせてやろうと思っていたのだが
but apparently you've become a failure.
とんだ出来損ないになったものだな
（モブ）
おい！
Hey.
Are you angry on Sho's behalf?
（鈴木）
ショウのために怒っているのか？
フフフ やはり お前は子供だ
You truly are a child.
Be quiet.
静かにしてろ
This is amusing, though.
Show me everything you've got.
だが 面白い
全力を出してみろ
（モブ）
あっ これは きつい
This is rough...
ふぐっ
Stop!
やめろ～！
Just sit there and watch.
そこで見ていろ
これが弱者の末路だ
This is what happens to weaklings.
Still, you sure have some nerve
to lecture me when you're so weak.
（鈴木）
しかし この程度で
私に説教していたのか？
You can't be serious.
冗談だろう？
（銃を起こす音）
（霊幻）動くな
Don't move.
弾は入ってるぜ
It's loaded, by the way.
Sakurai's Jugan.
（鈴木）
桜威の呪玩(じゅがん)か
You can't threaten me
with something like that.
私には脅しにもならんぞ
し… 師匠
M-Master...
Hey, Mob.
おう モブ
I don't sense any power from you.
（鈴木）
お前からは何の“力”も感じない
You'll stay out of this
if you know what's best for you.
引っ込んでいたほうが
身のためだぞ
まだ私の恐ろしさが
理解できんらしい
Apparently, you still don't
understand how powerful I am.
Hey, you alive, Mob?
（霊幻）
お～い 生きてるか？　モブ
I don't know what I was thinking,
letting you go off alone like that.
（霊幻）
お前１人で行かせるなんて
どうかしてたな
I think my ability to think
非日常的な状況で
思考力が落ちてたみたいだ
was impacted by all
the unnatural things going on.
師匠として情けない
I failed as a master.
You did well. I'll treat you to
some takoyaki on our way home.
よく頑張った
帰りにタコ焼き おごってやる
（モブ）
ハア…
よく頑張った
帰りにタコ焼き おごってやる
師匠だと？
Master?
Even though you can't even see
how powerful I am?
私の“力”すら
見えていないお前が？
So you're also someone
who tricks others and steals from them.
（鈴木）
つまり お前も人をダマして
搾取する側の人間ということか
Well, this is ironic.
（霊幻）
ハア… 皮肉なもんだ
If you ask me, you can only see
powers that can't be seen.
俺から言わせりゃ
お前のほうこそ―
“見えない力”しか見えてない
かわいそうなヤツだよ
I feel sorry for you.
What's that supposed to mean?
（鈴木）
どういう意味だ？
I'm saying ESP isn't the only
extraordinary power people can have.
（霊幻）
人が持つ優れた力ってのは―
超能力だけじゃないってことだよ
Off the top of my head,
お前を倒す方法も―
I can think of four ways to defeat you.
ざっと思いつくだけで
４通りあるしな
Oh? You should give them a try, then.
（鈴木）
ほう 試してみるといい
そんな気は もうない
Nah, I don't feel like it.
But I do have a request...
代わりに 俺から頼みが１つ
仲間に入れてくれないか？
Will you let me join you?
What good does that do me?
（鈴木）
私に何の得がある？
I'd be able to easily persuade my
student who's unconscious there,
（霊幻）
そこに倒れてる弟子も
外の連中も―
as well as all the guys outside.
俺なら うまく説得できる
That should be reason enough.
十分メリットになるだろ？
Let's hear about these methods
of defeating me as well...
（鈴木）
私を倒す方法とやらも聞いておこう
If you actually have any, that is.
本当にあるのならな
（霊幻）
超能力以外の―
I'll fill you in on some powers other
than ESP that you don't know about.
あんたの知らない力について
教えよう
The first power...
まず １つ目
超能力者が最も警戒すべき
人間の力
The power that espers should
be extremely cautious about...
That's...
それは―
腕力だよ バカ！
brute strength, you moron!
I guess I can see how you two
are master and student.
（鈴木）
このガキの師匠を名乗るだけはある
What a ridiculous combination.
くだらん師弟コンビだ
ま… 待て！　参った！
W-Wait! I give up!
I'll do anything you ask.
要望があれば何でも聞こう
You have put me in an extremely foul mood.
（鈴木）
私をここまで不快にさせるとは…
U-Um...
（霊幻）
あの… あの…
N-N-No, wait! Let's talk about—
（霊幻）
あっ いやいや だから 話を…
Sto—
（霊幻）やめ…
（爆発音）
何が起きてるんだ？
What's going on?
霊幻さん
Reigen-san...
間に合った
I made it in time.
I tried being courageous for once, President.
俺も今度は勇気を出してみたよ
社長
Serizawa... I see that you've
completely betrayed me now.
芹沢 完全に裏切ったか
ならば お前も…
In that case...
Forget it.
（モブ）
もういい
もう話さなくていい
That's enough talk.
Rage
ほう
Let me just tell you one last thing.
（モブ）
最後に１つ教えてやる
人の気持ちが分からないヤツは…
Those who don't understand
the feelings of others...
まあ いい
Never mind.
Sometimes you need to be
hurt to truly understand.
（モブ）
たまにはケガして学べ！
That's...
これは！
兄さんだ！
It's Nii-san.
Shigeo...
茂夫…
Mob's lost it.
モブがキレた
お… 俺も何か協力できるかな
I-Is there anything I can help with?
芹沢さん
Serizawa-san, take my master
and the others and evacuate.
師匠たちを連れて
ここから避難して！
制裁が先だ！
Punishment comes first!
Shigeo-kun!
（芹沢）
茂夫君！
That's...
（律）あれは？
（テル）マズい！
That's not good!
兄さんは？
Nii-san.
Plants?
植物？
So the boss really did cast Serizawa aside.
（峯岸(みねぎし)）
ボス やっぱり芹沢を切り捨てたね
誰？
Who?
悪いね 彼には借りがある
Sorry, but I owe him one.
Don't, Minegishi! If you piss off the boss...
（羽鳥(はとり)）
ヤバいって 峯岸！
ボスを怒らせたら…
羽鳥も無事だったか
So you're okay too, Hatori.
Minegishi, eh?
（鈴木）
峯岸か　ふん
Apparently, I'm now in a situation
where anyone can betray me.
もはや 誰が裏切るか
分からない状況だな
一度リセットするか
Back to the drawing board, I suppose.
Disappear.
（鈴木）
消えろ
Disappear. Disappear. Disappear.
消えろ 消えろ 消えろ！　フフフ
えらい気合いの入れようだな
Well, you're enthusiastic.
Output 10%
You're weak. Too weak.
（鈴木）
弱い　弱いぞ！
I'm still only using 10 percent of my powers.
私は まだ10パーセントの出力だ
Is that your 100 percent?
お前は
それが100パーセントなのか？
何だ ありゃ？
What the hell is that?
なるほどな
I see. So that's what you were after.
これに意識を向けていたのか
Now I'll be able to hit
you with everything...
これで思う存分ぶつけられる
My powers... and my rage.
この“力”
（モブ）
この怒りを！
I spilled a seed and lost sight of it
I'll find it using the color it's dyed in and watch it grow
It immediately returned to the palm of my hand
But it's still too light and too frail to reach for the skies
The world coldly drains away all the heat
The bright sunshine just isn't enough
The memories are closing off what lies ahead
Shake off their warmth and set off into the distance
If I let it wither, it'd be over just like that
But my hope just doesn't fade away
（霊幻）
キレたモブと―
The final battle begins between an enraged
Mob and the energy demon, Suzuki.
エネルギーの化け物(もん)鈴木との
最後の戦いが幕を開ける
Don't push yourself too hard, Mob.
あんまムチャすんじゃねえぞ
モブ
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 II Episode 13:
次回「モブサイコ100 Ⅱ」
第13話「ボス戦　最後の光」
"Boss Fight ~The Final Light~."
Watching the finale in real time
is an excellent decision.
最終回は
リアタイが正しい判断です
Boss Fight
~The Final Light~